{
	"data": [
        {
            "question": "This phone number is wrong. It ___ have six numbers, not five.\n",
            "a": "could",
            "b": "should",
            "c": "would",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "16",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "No one knows why the little boy ran into the busy road. He ___ to get an ice cream from the shop on the other side of the road.\n",
            "a": "couldn't have been trying",
            "b": "may have been trying",
            "c": "needn't have been trying",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "16",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "A: Rebecca didn't say much last night, did she?\nB: No. She ___ tired. I think she's working hard at the moment.\n",
            "a": "can't have been",
            "b": "should have been",
            "c": "might have been",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "16",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I'm so happy, I ___!\n",
            "a": "could cry",
            "b": "can cry",
            "c": "must cry",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "16",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why didn't you tell me that you wanted a sandwich? I ___ one for you when I made mine.\n",
            "a": "can't have made",
            "b": "could have made",
            "c": "could make",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "16",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "You're watching television with a friend but the sound is too low for you. You ask: '___ I turn the sound up a little, please?'\n",
            "a": "Would",
            "b": "Can",
            "c": "Should",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "16",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "You and a friend are arranging an evening together. You offer to cook dinner at your house. You ask: '___ dinner here?'\n",
            "a": "Could you have",
            "b": "Should you have",
            "c": "Would you like to have",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "16",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I suggested ___ the next day outside the hotel.\n",
            "a": "that we should meet",
            "b": "to meet",
            "c": "us to meet",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "16",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "___ you have time tomorrow, could you send these forms to Linda, please?\n",
            "a": "Could",
            "b": "Would",
            "c": "Should",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "16",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don't leave your glasses on the chair. Someone ___ sit on them.\n",
            "a": "should",
            "b": "may",
            "c": "must",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "16",
            "type": "2"
        }
    ]
}